

#### **SKILLS**

Languages

Python · Javascript · C++ · SQL · HTML

Database

MySQL · MS SQL · PostgreSQL ·

GeoDatabase

Data Analysis

Data visualisation · Data cleaning ·

**Statistics** 

Software Knowledge

 $\mathsf{Mulesoft} \cdot \mathsf{Tableau} \cdot \mathsf{Github} \cdot \mathsf{ESRI} \cdot$ 

Sharepoint

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

- A Excellent written and verbal communication
- B Time management
- C Creative thinking
- Problem solving
- E Continuous improvement
- F Excellent analytical

#### LANGUAGES

English

Proficient

Hungarian

Beginner

# SAIKHANTUYA ZORIGT

+36205858684 @zsaikhantuya@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

Master's student with at least 2 years of experience designing and developing in Python, C++, JavaScript, REST APIs, Agile methodology, and version control systems. Demonstrates strong problem- solving skills and a collaborative team environment. Seeking an opportunity to utilize my skills and experience in software development.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Master, Computer Science for Autonomous Systems

09/2020 - Ongoing

#### Systems

#### Eötvös Lorand University

Hungary

- Attended one year bachelor classes for foundation curriculum.
- Specializing in Computer science for Autonomous Systems, and focusing on image processing using Matlab, and C++.

## Bachelor, Environmental Remote Sensing

## 09/2014 - 07/2018

## National University of Mongolia

Mongolia

- Focused on google map API, and earthquake probability analysis in the district area.
- · Actively participated in conferences and won numerical studies competition

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Outsourcing Software Developer**

01/2020 - 10/2020

## **Novelsoft LLC**

Mongolia

Former software development department of IT Zone LLC

- Implemented the procurement of an emergency control notification system using the Mulesoft API, Javascript, and the ESRI portal. /Awarded employee of the month for this project.
- Útilized MS SQL, Tableau, Sharepoint, and other dashboard and visualization tools for data intelligence and analysis.

## Junior Software Developer

07/2018 - 12/2019

#### IT Zone LLC

Mongolia

- Participated in front-end development of the company's Location Tracking system, and Form Survey Web application using Angular, HTML, CSS, and Survey123 for ArcGIS.
- Implemented new functions to show reports and different map choices in the location tracking system. As a result, the website's UI/UX has been improved, and it is now possible to check truck fuel usage.

#### TRAINING / COURSES

## Python and Apps

From Morgan Stanley, organized by Code First Girls company

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**



## Employee of the Month

 ${\bf Successfully\ implemented\ Procurement,\ Emergency\ control\ notification\ system.}$ 



## Scholarship award

Granted Stipendium Hungaricum Scholarship